A Guide to the William M. Dietel papers FA1142
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2, 1982-1993
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Annual Meeting, 1990 March 29 (Box 46, Folder 363)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Adjourned Annual Meeting, 1990 September 21 (Box 46, Folder 364)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Annual Meeting, 1991 May 21 (Box 46, Folder 365)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1991 February 7 (Box 46, Folder 366)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1991 September 20 (Box 46, Folder 367)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1992 January 21 (Box 47, Folder 368)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1992 May 19 (Box 47, Folder 369)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1993 February 23 (Box 47, Folder 370)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1993 June 17 (Box 47, Folder 371)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Joint Meeting of Board Program Meeting & Board Property Committee, 1988 January 26 (Box 47, Folder 372)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Greenways in the Hudson River Valley, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 373)
  - The Hunger Project, 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 374)
  - The Indicator, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 375)
  - Institute of International Education, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 376)
  - Institute for Public Policy Research (IPPR), 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 377)
  - Institute for 21st Century Studies, 1987-1989, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 378-379)
  - International Biotechnology Group, Inc., 1988 April (Box 48, Folder 380)
  - International Fund for Agricultural Research (IFAR), 1987-1990 (Box 48, Folder 381-384)
  - International Institute for Media and Development, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 385)
  - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA), 1989 (Box 49, Folder 386)
  - International Management and Development Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 387)
  - International Policy on Agriculture and Trade, GATT, 1988-1991 (Box 49, Folder 388)
  - International Trypanotolerance Centre, 1982, 1984, 1988-1991 (Box 49, Folder 389-391)
  - International Trypanoltoerance Centre, 1982, 1984, 1988-1991 (Box 50, Folder 392)
  - International Women's Health Coalition, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 393)
  - International Youth Foundation, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 394)
  - Interphil, 1989-1991 (Box 50, Folder 395-396)
  - James Irvine Foundation, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 397-398)
  - International Service for Agricultural Research (ISNAR), 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 399)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc., 1989-1991 (Box 51, Folder 400)
  - Kiser Research, Inc., 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 401)
  - Latin American Scholarship Program of American Universities, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 402)
  - Lincoln University, 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 403)
  - The Loomis Chaffee School, 1987-1988, 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 404)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 405)
  - Mahoney, Brooke, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 406)
  - Merkling, Chris, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 407)
  - Mexico Equity Trust, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 408)
  - The Robert Muller School, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 409)
  - National Audubon Society, 1987-1990 (Box 52, Folder 410)
  - National Center for Nonprofit Boards, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 411)
  - National Institute for Citizen Participation and Negotiation, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 412)
  - The Nature Conservancy, 1987-1988 (Box 52, Folder 413)
  - Natureplace, Michael Sweatman, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 414)
  - The New York Botanical Garden, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 415)
  - North American Institute, 1989-1991 (Box 52, Folder 416)
  - The Oak Foundation (U. K.) Limited, 1987-1988 (Box 52, Folder 417)
  - Open University, United Kingdom, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 418)
  - Overseas Development Council, 1989, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 419)
  - Partners, 1988-1991 (Box 53, Folder 420)
  - Partners for Sacred Places, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 421)
  - Peace Garden Project, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 422)
  - American Philanthropy, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 423)
  - Philanthropy Newsletter, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 424)
  - The Philanthropic Initiative, Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 425)
  - Philippine-American Foundation, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 426)
  - Pocantico Estate, 1988-1990 (Box 53, Folder 427-429)
  - Pocantico Estate, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 430-432)
  - Pocantico Institute, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 433)
  - President's Rural Advisory Council, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 434)
  - Private Assistance in International Development, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 435)
  - The Quiet Revolution Project, 1988-1991 (Box 54, Folder 436)
  - The Quiet Revolution Project, 1988-1991 (Box 55, Folder 437-438)
  - Readers Digest Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 439)
  - Regional Environmental Center for Central and Eastern Europe, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 440)
  - Resources Development Foundation, 1988-1990 (Box 55, Folder 441-442)
  - Resources Management Consultants, Inc., 1988-1990 (Box 55, Folder 443)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center, 1988-1991 (Box 55, Folder 444)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center, 1988-1991 (Box 56, Folder 445-446)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center, Governing Council Meeting, 1988 April 5-October 25 (Box 56, Folder 447-448)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 449)
  - Rockefeller & Company, Inc., 1988-1990 (Box 56, Folder 450)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1987-1991 (Box 56, Folder 451)
  - Rockefeller Cousins' Philanthropy Yearbook, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 452)
  - Rockefeller Cousins' Philanthropy Yearbook, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 452A)
    Restricted from access-Confidential materials
  - Rockefeller University, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 453)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1987-1991 (Box 56, Folder 454)
  - Rockefeller, David, Jr., 1987-1990 (Box 57, Folder 455-456)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1988-1991 (Box 57, Folder 457)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1988-1990 (Box 57, Folder 458)
  - Rockefeller, Winthrop Paul, 1988-1991 (Box 57, Folder 459)
  - Rodale Institute, Robert Rodale, 1987-1989 (Box 57, Folder 460)
  - Joseph Rowntree Charitable Trust, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 461)
  - Rural Economic Analysis Program, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1989-1992 (Box 57, Folder 462-464)
  - Sadat Peace Foundation, 1988-1991 (Box 58, Folder 465)
  - Santa Fe Institute, 1988-1990 (Box 58, Folder 466)
  - SCH Consultants, 1991 December (Box 58, Folder 467)
  - Society for Values in Higher Education, 1990-1991 (Box 58, Folder 468)
  - South Africa, 1988-1990 (Box 58, Folder 469)
  - South African Advanced Education and Training Project, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 58, Folder 470)
  - Spears, Benzak, Saloman, & Farrel, Inc., 1985, 1987-1990 (Box 58, Folder 471)
  - Surdna Foundation, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 471)
  - Sustainable Agriculture, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 472)
  - Synergos Institute, 1988, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 473)
  - T. K. International, Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 58, Folder 474)
  - U. S. Council of Mecico-U. S. Business Committee, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 475)
  - USDA Publications Agricultural Research Service Program Plan, 1983, 1985, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 476)
  - United World Colleges, 1990-1991 (Box 59, Folder 477)
  - University of Chicago, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 478)
  - Venrock, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 479)
  - Warrior International, 1988-1993 (Box 59, Folder 480-482)
  - WETA, 1988-1992 (Box 59, Folder 483)
  - WETA, 1988-1992 (Box 60, Folder 484-487)
  - WETA, Report of Long Range Planning Committee, 1989-1993, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 488)
  - Winrock International, 1988-1990 (Box 60, Folder 489)
  - Winrock International, 1988-1990 (Box 61, Folder 490)
  - Winrock International, Board Information, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 491)
  - Winrock International, Board of Directors Meeting, 1987 May 7-8-1989 November 17-18 (Box 61, Folder 492-496)
  - Winrock International, Board of Directors Meeting, 1990 May 10-11-1991 December 5-6 (Box 62, Folder 497-501)
  - Winrock International, Board of Directors Meeting, 1992 May 8-9 (Box 63, Folder 502)
  - Winrock International, Board Members, 1991-1993 (Box 63, Folder 503)
  - Winrock International, President/CEO Search, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 504)
  - Winrock International, Nominating Committee Meeting, 1988 October 26 (Box 63, Folder 505)
  - Winrock International, Nominating Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 63, Folder 506)
  - Winrock International, African Women's Project, 1989, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 507)
  - Winrock International, Arkansas Advisory Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 63, Folder 508)
  - Winrock International, Development Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 63, Folder 509)
  - Winrock International, Development Committee, 1988-1992 (Box 64, Folder 510-514)
  - Winrock International, Development Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 515-516)
  - Winrock International, Executive Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 617)
  - Winrock International, Institute for Agricultural Research, 1989-1991 (Box 65, Folder 518-520)
  - Winrock International, Institute for Agricultural Research, 1989-1991 (Box 66, Folder 521)
  - Winrock International, Investment Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 522)
  - Winrock International, Investment Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 66, Folder 523-525)
  - Winrock International, General Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 66, Folder 526)
  - Winrock International, Bob Havener Correspondence, 1987, 1989-1993 (Box 67, Folder 527)
  - Winrock International, Papers & Publications, 1986-1993 (Box 67, Folder 528)
    - Winrock International, Papers & Publications, 1986-1993
      Oversized architectural drawing-Land ownership on Petit Jean Mountain, Conway County, Arkansas, 1986 April 11
  - Winrock International, Projects, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 529)
  - Winrock International, Project Summary Statements, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 530)
  - Winrock International, Program Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 67, Folder 531)
  - Winrock International, Program Plan, 1990-1992 (Box 67, Folder 532)
  - Winrock International, World Food Prize, 1990-1992 (Box 67, Folder 533)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 534)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust, 1988-1991 (Box 68, Folder 535-539)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 540-541)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust, Financial Information, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 542)
  - Women's World Banking, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 543)
  - Woodrow Wilson Center, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 544)
  - Robert Woodruff Foundation, Inc., 1988 (Box 69, Folder 545)
  - World Academy Art & Science, 1988, 1990-1992 (Box 69, Folder 546)
  - World Council of Churches, 1990-1992 (Box 69, Folder 547)
  - World Vision, 1986-1988, 1990 (Box 69, Frame 548)
  - Worldwatch Institute, 1986, 1988-1991 (Box 69, Folder 549)
  - WNYC Public Radio, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 550)
- Accession 3, 1987-1996
  - African-American Institute, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 551)
  - Airspace, Association of Independents in Radio, 1992-1993 (Box 70, Folder 552)
  - American Farmland Trust, Suit, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 553)
  - American Farmland Trust, 1989-1994 (Box 70, Folder 555-557)
  - American Farmland Trust, Development, 1990-1993 (Box 70, Folder 558-559)
  - American Farmland Trust, Development, 1990-1993 (Box 71, Folder 560)
  - American Farmland Trust, 1991-1992, 1994-1995 (Box 71, Folder 561-563)
  - American Farmland Trust, Board of Directors and President's Council Nominating Committee Prospects, 1992 May 31 (Box 71, Folder 564)
  - American Farmland Trust, Nominating Committee Prospects, 1993 September 26 (Box 71, Folder 565)
  - American Farmland Trust, Board of Directors' Meeting, 1993 May 16-17 (Box 71, Folder 566)
  - American Farmland Trust, Campaign for America's Farmland, Volunteer Handbook, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 567)
  - American Friends of the British Museum, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 568-570)
  - American Public Radio, Board of Directors' Meeting, 1989 February-June (Box 72, Folder 571-572)
  - American Public Radio, Board of Directors' Meeting, 1990 February-1991 June (Box 73, Folder 573-577)
  - American Public Radio, Board of Directors' Meeting, 1991 October-1993 February (Box 74, Folder 578-582)
  - American Public Radio, Board Retreat Sessions, 1990 February 8-9 (Box 74, Folder 583)
  - American Public Radio, Press Clippings, 1989 October (Box 74, Folder 584)
  - American Public Radio, Board of Directors' Meeting, 1993 June-October (Box 75, Folder 585-586)
  - American Public Radio, Strategy for a New Century, 1993 June 7-14 (Box 75, Folder 587-588)
  - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1990-1994 (Box 75, Folder 589-590)
  - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1990-1994 (Box 76, Folder 591-596)
  - The Brookings Institution, Sustainable Development Conference, 1992-1993 (Box 77, Folder 597)
  - Cambridge College, 1992-1993 (Box 77, Folder 598)
  - Campaign for Oxford, 1992-1993 (Box 77, Folder 599)
  - Center for Community Change, Publications, 1989-1993 (Box 77, Folder 600-601)
  - Center for Law & Social Policy, 1993-1994 (Box 77, Folder 602)
  - Center on Philanthropy, 1992-1993 (Box 77, Folder 603)
  - Children's Defense Fund, 1987 July (Box 77, Folder 604)
  - CIVICUS, 1993-1994 (Box 77, Folder 605-606)
  - CIVICUS, North American Report, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 607)
  - CIVICUS, Other Regional Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 608)
  - CIVICUS, Board Members/Organizing Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 78, Folder 609)
  - CIVICUS, Board of Directors, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 610)
  - CIVICUS, By-Laws, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 611)
  - CIVICUS, Development, 1991-1993 (Box 79, Folder 612)
  - CIVICUS, Initial Meeting of the Founding Board, 1993 May 29-31 (Box 79, Folder 612)
  - CIVICUS, Report Committee Meeting, 1993 March 26-28 (Box 79, Folder 613)
  - CIVICUS, Meeting/Materials, 1992-1993 (Box 79, Folder 614)
  - CIVICUS, Organizing Committee Meeting, 1992 October 9-11-1993 January 22-24 (Box 79, Folder 615-616)
  - CIVICUS, Executive and Search Committee Meetings, 1993 November 2 (Box 79, Folder 617)
  - CIVICUS, Progress Report, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 618)
  - CIVICUS, Executive Director Search, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 619)
  - CIVICUS, Budapest, 1991, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 620)
  - CIVICUS, Resurrecting Interphil, 1992-1993 (Box 79, Folder 621)
  - CIVICUS, Death of Interphil, 1990-1991 (Box 79, Folder 622)
  - CIVICUS, 1993 November 3-5 (Box 80, Folder 623)
  - Citizen Democracy Corps, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 624)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1990-1995 (Box 80, Folder 625-627)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Foundation Board and Committee Agendas, 1993 April 22-24-November 11-13 (Box 81, Folder 628-629)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Board of Trustees, 1993 November 13 (Box 81, Folder 630)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Board of Trustees Retreat, 1994 April 21 (Box 81, Folder 631)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Nominating Comnmittee, 1992 November 13-1993 November 13 (Box 81, Folder 632-634)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1994 Financial Plan, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 635)
  - Committee on Agricultural Sustainability for Developing Countries, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 636)
  - Commonwealth Fund, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 637)
  - Concord Academy/Earthwatch, 1992 March 15 (Box 81, Folder 638)
  - The Conservation Fund, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 639)
  - Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 640)
  - Cornell International Institute for Food, Agriculture and Development (CIIFAD), 1992-1993 (Box 81, Folder 641)
  - Council on Foundations, 1988-1992, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 642)
  - Center for Racial Equality and Democratic Opportunity, Inc. (CREDO), 1992 (Box 81, Folder 643)
  - Dana Farber Cancer Center, 1990, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 644)
  - Diamond, Henry, Sustainable Use of Land, 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 645)
  - Dorchester Counseling Center, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 646)
  - Dublin City University, TARA Consultants, LTD., 1992-1995 (Box 82, Folder 647-648)
  - Earth Force, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 649)
  - Earthwatch, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 650)
  - Eastern Europe, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 651)
  - Ecoshare, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 652)
  - Ecotrust (Box 82, Folder 653)
  - Ecumenical Development Initiative, 1989-1994 (Box 82, Folder 654)
  - Ecumenical Development Initiative, 1989-1994 (Box 83, Folder 655)
  - The Edison Project, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 656)
  - Epperly, Robert, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 657)
  - Ethics Resource Center, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 658)
  - Eurasia Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 659)
  - European Foundation Center, 1992-1994 (Box 83, Folder 660)
  - Foundation for the Development of Polish Agriculture, 1988, 1991-1996 (Box 83, Folder 661-662)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture, Board Meeting, 1990 November 28-29 (Box 84, Folder 663)
  - Forrest Lake Camp, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 664)
  - Hartford Gunn Institute, 1993, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 665)
  - Hershey School, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 666)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, 1993-1995 (Box 84, Folder 667)
  - Independent Sector, 1990-1994 (Box 84, Folder 668)
  - Inforum, 1989-1995 (Box 84, Folder 669-672)
  - Inforum, 1990-1994 (Box 85, Folder 673-675)
  - Inforum, Board Meeting, 1994 July 30-31 (Box 85, Folder 676)
  - International Alliance, 1992-1993 (Box 85, Folder 677)
  - International Alliance, 1992-1993 (Box 86, Folder 678)
  - International Networking Meeting, 1991 May 28 (Box 86, Folder 679)
  - Sustainable Land-Use Systems Research, 1990 September 30 (Box 86, Folder 680)